bunkrapp.com 2015-12-28

# Privacy Policy of Bunkr - Bunkr

## Privacy Policy

Bunkr is committed to safeguarding the Personal Data of Users. This privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) is part of the Terms & Conditions. By using the Bunkr' Service, Users agree to abide and be bound by this Privacy Policy, which may be modified or updated from time to time without notice. In this event the update will be displayed on the Service. 

Bunkr is owned and operated by ALFLED S.A.S. a simplified stock company, registered with the Trade and Corporate Registry of Rouen under the number 538 703 513, with its main office located 72 Rue de la République 76140 Le Petit-Quevilly (France). It is Bunkr's policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our Service, located at http://bunkrapp.com/. 

Collectively, the website, and any other Bunkr services (including, without limitation, mobile software and applications) are hereinafter referred to as the "Service". This Privacy Policy describes how Bunkr uses personal information of users collected through our Service. 

PLEASE READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY CAREFULLY. BY ACCESSING OR USING THE SERVICE, YOU ACKNOWLEDGE THAT YOU HAVE READ, UNDERSTOOD, AND AGREE TO BE BOUND TO ALL THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND OUR TERMS OF USE. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THESE TERMS AND CONDITIONS, PLEASE EXIT, AND DO NOT ACCESS OR USE, THE SERVICE. 

#### Website Visitors

Like most Service operators, Bunkr collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Bunkr’ purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Bunkr’ visitors use its Service. From time to time, Bunkr may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its Service. 

Bunkr also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users. Bunkr only discloses logged in user IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below. 

#### Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to Bunkr in ways that require Bunkr to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Bunkr gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up for an account at Bunkr to provide a username and email address. Bunkr collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with Bunkr. Bunkr does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Service-related activities.   
If authorized by you, we may also access profile and other information from services like Facebook.   
Our systems may associate this personal information with your activities in the course of providing service to you (such as pages you view or things you click on or search for).   
We do not knowingly contact or collect personal information from children under 13. If you believe we have inadvertently collected such information, please contact us so we can promptly obtain parental consent or remove the information. 

#### Access

You can sign into your account to see, update, or delete any personally identifiable information we have stored, such as your username, name, address, email. You can also contact us by email to request to see or delete this information. 

#### Deletion

We may keep non-personally-identifying information or personally-identifying information or others data indefinitely. 

#### Sharing

We generally do not share personally identifiable information (such as name, address, email) with other companies for marketing purposes. 

#### Location

We do not collect, use or share your precise geographic location. 

#### Aggregated Statistics

Bunkr may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its Service. For instance, Bunkr may monitor the most popular decks on the Bunkr Service. Bunkr may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Bunkr does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. 

#### Vendors

Analytics companies may access anonymous data (such as your IP address or device ID) to help us understand how our services are used. They use this data solely on our behalf. They do not share it except in aggregate form; no data is shared as to any individual user. 

#### Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

Bunkr discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Bunkr’ behalf or to provide services available at Bunkr’ Service, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Bunkr’ Service, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Bunkr will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Bunkr discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when Bunkr believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Bunkr, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an Bunkr Service and have supplied your email address, Bunkr may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with Bunkr and our products. We primarily use our product blog to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Bunkr takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information. 

#### Security

We take reasonable steps to secure your personally identifiable information against unauthorized access or disclosure. We encrypt transmission of data on pages where you provide payment information. However, no security or encryption method can be guaranteed to protect information from hackers or human error.   
Information we collect may be stored or processed on computers located in any country where we do business. 

#### Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a Service stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the Service each time the visitor returns. Bunkr uses cookies to help Bunkr identify and track visitors, their usage of Bunkr Service, and their Service access preferences. Bunkr visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Bunkr Service, with the drawback that certain features of the Bunkr Service may not function properly without the aid of cookies. 

#### Business Transfers

If Bunkr, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Bunkr goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Bunkr may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy. 

#### Third Parties Cookies

Content appearing on any of our Service may be delivered to users by third parties services (e.g. Google, Facebook, Twitter and many others), who may set cookies. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by Bunkr and does not cover the use of cookies by any third parties. 

#### Privacy Policy Changes

This privacy policy was last updated on 02-04-2015. Our privacy policy may change from time to time. If we make any material changes to our policies, we will place a prominent notice on our Service or application. If the change materially affects registered users, we will send a notice to you by email, push notification or text. 

Please contact us if you have any questions or comments about our privacy practices or this Privacy Policy. You can reach us online at [support@bunkr.me](mailto:support@bunkr.me?subject=Privacy+Policy+of+Bunkr). 

Effective as of 02-04-2015  
Updated 02-04-2015
